Sheldon R. Johnson

3742 W Roberts St Milwaukee, WI 53208 414-595-9292 sheldonj2006@gmail.com

Executive Summary:

Flexible and resourceful machine operator who has maintained perfect attendance and safety records throughout a five-year career. Experienced in diverse machining operations as well as forklift, hand cart and pallet jack use. Desires a role in assembly or packaging in a warehouse setting.

Experience:

Kleen Test Products

Port Washington, WI 06/2014 to Present

Machine Operator/Packaging

- Set up machines at the beginning of shift to ensure proper working order
- Perform testing procedures to ensure that machines work optimally during the production procedures
- · Maintain and clean machines before and after each shift
- Feed information akin to speed, shapes and sizes through the machine set up box
- Place parts in semi-automated and bindery machines
- · Calibrate machines at the beginning of each shift
- · Recalibrating machines at the end of each shift
- Monitor machines during every procedure to ensure optimum running
- Troubleshoot problems during machine operation
- Ensure that regular and preventative maintenance procedures are carried out
- Perform random tests to ensure accuracy
- Perform safety checks on every machine
- · Ensure that machines are producing quality products by managing periodic checks on output
- Ensure stocks of needed materials are ready and available at all times
- Create and maintain activity logs
- Provide relevant information regarding progress to supervisors

Quad Graphics Sussex, WI Cover Deck Feeder 02/2011 to 06/2014

ŸWorked on high speed machine equipment's and precision machinery used in mass production of a firm ŸMonitored the machine regularly to prevent any chances of breaking down Performed regular checks on the parts of machinery and made important adjustments wherever necessary

ŸMade sure the products manufactured from the machine are of high quality and made adjustments to improve the quality

ŸPrepared the machine for starting the production process by equipping it with the required tools

YMade sure the constant availability of raw materials and inputs so that the machine can function constantly

YWorked over time to complete the production requirement of the clients

BuySeasons New Berlin, WI Order Picker 09/2007 to 09/2008

Fed Ex

New Berlin, WI

Parcel Assistant

09/2006 to 08/2009

Education:

Juneau High School Milwaukee, WI **Diploma** 2006

References: Available upon request